<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<T3locallangExt>
	<data type="array">
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
			<label index="title.description">Geben Sie den den Namen dieser zusätzlichen systemweiten Spracherweiterung an.</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">Diese Option versteckt die systemweite Spracherweiterung innerhalb des Backend. Backend Benutzern steht somit diese Systemsprache nicht zur Verfügung.</label>
			<label index=".description">Definiert, welche alternativen Sprachen auf den einzelnen Webseiten verfügbar sind.</label>
			<label index=".details">Die Web&gt;Seite Erweiterung bietet Backend Benutzern die Möglichkeit, Seiteninhalte nicht nur spaltenweise sondern auch nach Sprachen getrennt zu editieren. Die verfügbaren Sprachen werden durch die zuvor angelegten alternativen Seitensprachen definiert.</label>
		</languageKey>
	</data>
	<orig_hash type="array">
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
			<label index="title.description" type="integer">111675524</label>
			<label index="hidden.description" type="integer">199895530</label>
			<label index=".description" type="integer">1687697</label>
			<label index=".details" type="integer">190956227</label>
		</languageKey>
	</orig_hash>
	<orig_text type="array">
		<languageKey index="de" type="array">
			<label index="title.description">Enter the name of this additional system language.</label>
			<label index="hidden.description">This option will hide the system language from being available in the backend.</label>
			<label index=".description">Defines which languages are alternatively available on each webpage.</label>
			<label index=".details">The Web&gt;Page module has a feature which allows users to edit page content divided into not only columns but also languages. The languages available for translation are determined by the number of Website Language record created.
For a webpage to be available in another language an &quot;Alternative Page Language&quot; record must be created on the page.</label>
		</languageKey>
	</orig_text>
</T3locallangExt>